[Episode 8]
You have great taste.
My mom really liked the scarf.
I think you succeeded.
If you were trying to seduce me, you're doing well.
I'm starting to become interested in you.
But this is the end.
I'm too grown up to be seduced by a playboy like you.
Unfortunately, I can now distinguish love from passion.
[Song Eunchae]
Did you sleep well, Eunchae?
- Warm, fresh seaweed rolls for sale!
- Rice cakes!
Thank you.
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Rice cakes for sale!
Galchi, should we sing the seaweed rolls song?
Sure!
1, 2, 3, 4!
♪ Roll me tightly ♪
♪ Press me gently ♪
♪ Like rice within the roll ♪
♪ I want to stick right onto you ♪
♪ Hold me ♪
I'm gonna go make a phone call.
♪ I want to stick right onto you ♪
Hello?
Minchae.
Eunchae!
Are Mom and Dad doing well?
Tell them not to worry, because I'm doing fine.
Yeah, I'm really okay.
- Who's that?
- You should have called.
Is that Eunchae? Hey, Eunchae?
Give it here! Give it to me! I'm still talking to her!
- Listen to your mother.
- Listen to your big sister.
Give it to me now!
Eunchae. It's Mom. Have you eaten?
Hey, Eunchae. It's me. I shrunk your panties.
Come home soon.
Eunchae, Sukchae took your cell
and made international calls.
Hey, stop!
We're going to move out, Eunchae!
We're going to move out even if
we have to borrow lots of money,
so come home as soon as you can.
Come home soon!
I'm really doing well, Mom.
I will return tough as a rock.
So don't worry and take care. Okay?
Have you any love for your sister?
You were so unloving towards her over the phone.
I should a lotto ticket
while I'm out at the grocery store.
If I win, I'll buy a house twice
this size just across the street.
Mom, if you got less face lifts and
less botox, we'd be rich by now.
We'd own a building by now.
I hear you.
What about you?
You don't earn a single penny
yet use your dad and sister's
credit cards to buy expensive clothes and shoes!
If it weren't for you, we would be rich, you idiot!
I agree.
Hello?
Yun!
What brings you to this dump, superstar Yun?
May I join you for dinner?
I wanted to have dinner with you.
Sure, come sit here.
Have you heard from Eunchae?
Speaking of, just a while ago...
No. She didn't call.
You came to check up on Eunchae, huh?
Check up? No, no.
But that girl must be nuts!
She doesn't even know how dangerous it is out there.
She's immature yet doesn't know fear.
Mrs. Song. Are you just going to sit there?
Shouldn't you file a missing person's report?
A girl is like a porcelain bowl.
Once outside, she will get smashed.
Just finish your food.
Whether Eunchae picks her ear with a streetlight pole
or peel an apple with a nail clipper, what's it to you?
Exactly.
Rice cakes! We have fresh and warm rice cake!
Seaweed rolls! Buy seaweed rolls!
Buy seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls!
Awesome tasting seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls! They're delicious!
Don't go.
Don't go, Eunchae.
I won't burden you.
My sister makes really good seaweed rolls,
but she doesn't make good kimchi.
Make me kimchi before you go.
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Hold on. Do it for me too.
You have some on your face too.
Yun Seo-kyeong.
Muhyeok.
Brother.
And Galchi.
[Our countree...]
That's not right.
Dear Lord,
if you really do exist,
I promise you this.
About Song Eunchae.
If you'll let me have her for my remaining days...
Three servings of crab sticks.
And four radishes. And one of those.
Give us a bit of a discount! Thank you.
If you let her comfort me for the time I have left...
If you don't hurt me again...
I could stop everything right now.
Uncle!
Good night.
The hatred, the anger, I'll let it all go.
And go in peace.
Lord, I make this promise to you.
Damn it, isn't this crow's feet?
Oh, no! What do I do?
Eunchae! I got a crow's feet!
Eunchae!
I don't like this style.
Flower shirts don't look good on me.
They're my least favorite clothes.
I'm sorry, I didn't know. I'll go look for other ones.
- Eunchae!
- Yunchae!
Your favorite flavor of ice cream. Eat up.
Slow down.
Who's this?
She's a good friend.
But I don't think she's doing well.
She had an accident when she was young.
She's very kind and nice.
So are you staying at her house now?
Yeah.
Give it to me.
Oh, hold on.
This'll is probably about $200, right?
You don't even have money?
Don't you have a credit card?
Oh yeah, Sukjae took your credit cards.
Hey...
- My sister bought it.
- It's mine!
Isn't it really hard to get over Yun?
Not really,
I guess it's stupid of me to ask.
But really, I think I'm very much over Yun now.
You don't have to lie to me!
You don't think I know love?
I'm going to use the bathroom.
Okay. Do you want me to come with you?
No, it's okay.
When I closed my eyes to sleep, I always saw Yun.
Whether Yun was with me or not, he was all I could see.
I told you, I know how you feel.
But now, I see someone else.
Sometimes I still see Yun,
but now I keep seeing the other person.
Who is it?
Oh, my! Galchi!
Huh? Galchi?
Oh, no! I was to meet with Galchi's teacher.
I'll be right back. Take care of Seo-kyeong!
Galchi's teacher?
Hello?
Yeah, Mom.
What? Laundry? You left it on top of the stove?
I'm not at home now.
Can't you try Sukchae? Where are you?
Okay. I'll go home right now,
Galchi!
Eunchae!
Sorry, did you wait long?
Come on. The teacher must be waiting.
I don't have to go to school.
Who's going to sell the seaweed rolls?
Well, I can help your mom, or your uncle can help.
I'm sure there are others who can help your mom.
You can go to school without any worries, okay?
Let's go.
Nervous?
Here.
Let's go.
I'll be right back. I have to pee
and turn off the stove. Stay here.
Don't go anywhere, just stay put.
Okay.
Wow! Fish!
Fishie! Fishie!
I'm so tired. When are we doing the radio show?
7:30 p.m.
- I'll see you at around 6:30 then.
- Okay.
I'll see you in a bit.
Fishie!
Hey.
Hey!
Who are you?
Who are you, and why are you on my property?
Who...
Hey... That pin! I got it for Eunchae on her birthday!
This?
Where did you get it?
Eunchae gave it to me earlier.
You know Eunchae?
Yeah.
You saw her?
Is Eunchae home?
No.
Where is Eunchae?
Ice cream.
Huh?
Wow! A waterfall!
Waterfall!
Song Minchae! What happened?
Where are you now?
We got a problem!
Yun has taken her hostage.
What?
Yun said if you want her back,
then you have to come here yourself.
Roar! Roar!
Isn't he cute?
Want it?
It's all right.
Have a lollipop.
Wait a minute. Is this one cuter?
Which one do you like better?
Did you talk to Eunchae?
Yes.
Is there anything else you want to eat?
This one? Here.
Don't go.
Don't go, Eunchae.
I won't burden you. Don't go.
Wow! She's so pretty!
Yummy, yummy!
Wow!
So pretty!
Necklace.
Oh, no...
Minchae!
Hello.
Why are you standing there like you
have to go to the bathroom?
Um... I'm just...
What are you doing? Do you have to go number two?
No! I just went!
- Is Yun home yet?
- Yes.
Son! My son!
How was your day? Did you have a good day?
Mom, I'm so tired.
Why? What is it? Because of Eunchae?
- Forget it.
- I want to go home.
Oh! It's the pretty lady!
Who is she?
What the... That's my necklace! It's my necklace!
Miss, who are you? Which room were you in?
There.
Yun! Who is this girl?
Just someone I know. Don't scare her, Mom.
I don't think she's normal.
Stay here. Don't move.
They didn't say where they were going?
No. She told me to go home,
and that she would be home with Mom soon.
I'll be back.
When Eunchae comes, tell her not to go anywhere.
Okay.
I want to go home.
I want to go back home.
Galchi, Galchi.
Don't cry, don't cry!
Why did you have to call the cops?
You could've just asked her nicely.
She keeps denying that she took it!
Galchi! Galchi!
Where did you hide the ring?
You're not going to give it back?
Galchi!
I think she really doesn't know.
Why don't you go look for it again?
I looked everywhere!
You know how much that diamond ring costs?
It's priceless!
Yun, why did you bring someone
like that into the house?
Why did you bring a freak like her here
and cause this mess?
Have you seen a small, twinkling, ring?
Think about it.
I want to go home.
I think she's a pro, just acting like she's dumb.
Did you hide it in your clothes?
Or maybe you swallowed it?
Galchi...
Confess before the cops come
and make it more serious.
If you confess now,
I'll forgive you without pressing charges.
Tell me now!
Uncle! Uncle!
What's the problem?
I've been waiting for you forever!
I've lost a six-carat diamond ring.
I'm sorry, but could you take your socks off?
Don't just frisk her. I told you.
She hid it in her clothes!
Strip search her.
You don't have evidence.
That's a violation of her rights.
Thieves don't have rights!
Where did you hide it?
Seriously, where did you hide it? Huh?
Uncle!
You should have listened when I was asking nicely!
Come on! Take this off, too!
I don't want to! No!
I don't want to. Galchi! Galchi!
Mister. I... Well...
Where is my sister? Did she go home?
No. She's inside.
Mister!
Uncle!
Mr. Cha!
What? You know her?
Get on my back.
Dear Lord,
if you really do exist,
I promise you this.
Mister.
Let's go home.
Mommy!
Mommy.
If you'll let me have her for my remaining days...
Song Eunchae.
Let go. Let go!
Mister.
If you let her comfort me for the time I have left...
Mister!
If you don't hurt me again...
I could stop everything right now.
Mister!
The hatred, the anger, I'll let it all go.
And go in peace.
Lord, I make this promise to you.
What the...
You were at Muhyeok's place this whole time?
Were you staying with Muhyeok this whole time?
Are you insane?
Don't yell.
Eunchae.
Why are you yelling?
Why are you yelling at me?
What did I ever do to you to get yelled at?
And no, I'm not insane. I'm doing just fine, Yun.
What's wrong with you?
You're not acting like yourself!
You messed up today.
To Seo-kyeong and Muhyeok.
You did them wrong, big time.
That stupid girl was Mr. Cha's older sister?
Goodness. Regardless, she's a thief.
It's not like the ring grew legs
and walked off by itself.
Oh. My blood pressure's rising!
My ring! What about my ring?
What do I do?
I found something that's not ring nor a necklace.
What? What is that?... Bring it here.
[Forever]
What is it? Bring it here. What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
What will I do about my ring? Goodness...
My ring!
[Forever]
[Together]
She lost consciousness early,
so she wouldn't know she gave birth to twins.
You and I will have to take this secret to our graves.
Everything about today.
I'm going to tell her the baby died.
They weren't meant to be with their mother.
[Forever]
Build me a son, O Lord.
Who will be strong enough to know when he is weak,
and brave enough to face himself when he is afraid,
one who will be proud and unbending in honest defeat...
Lead him, I pray, not in the path of ease and comfort,
but under the stress and spur of
difficulties and challenge...
Here, let him learn to stand up in the storm.
A son who'll master himself before
he seeks to master other men,
one who'll reach into the future,
yet never forget the past.
Who is that guy?
I trust and support my son's decision
one hundred percent.
If Yun chose her, I'm sure she's a good girl.
We don't have a mother.
We don't have a mother!
Mommy! Mommy!
Where are you going, Eunchae?
Just out for a walk and to get some fresh air.
My ring.
Mom, don't get sick over such a trivial thing.
Do you know how much it cost?
I'll go buy you one.
I'll go out and buy you one, okay?
It's not something you can just go out and buy.
Let's eat some noodles, Eunchae.
Let's make some noodles!
Move!
Come on! Let's make noodles!
Didn't you hear me?
Noodles! Let's have noodles!
You eat it! Stuff yourself full with them!
What's wrong with you?
Are you on drugs?
You are, aren't you?
If I had, I would have killed you by now!
Song Eunchae!
How old are you? Grow up!
Noodles? How could you be hungry at a time like this?
Because of you, some of us can't eat nor sleep.
Why is that my fault, you brat?
Why is everyone blaming me?
Why only me?
You're pathetic, Yun.
You're an embarrassment.
You better not go. You better not leave.
Come back here!
I'm not some dog that comes and goes
when you say so, you jerk!
Song Eunchae!
Mommy!
Are you okay, Mom?
Should I go out and buy some medicine?
Mommy. Mom...
Galchi!
Eunchae!
Didn't you go to school?
No. Mom's really sick.
Your mom is sick?
I'm going to get some medicine right now.
Still, you should go to school.
Where is your uncle?
I don't know. He was gone when I woke up.
I'll be right back after I get the medicine.
Seo-kyeong.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry...
I didn't steal the ring. I didn't steal it.
I know. I know.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, Yun. Yeah. I asked around.
I don't think I can get exactly the same one
as your mom's,
but I can probably get a similar one.
Huh? I'm going out right now.
If you get there earlier, just window shop.
I was curious about something.
I have something to ask you.
What's the difference between passion and love?
For example, is this passion?
I love you.
It just happened. I love you.
Why did she hang up suddenly?
Did she get on the elevator?
It's so complicated. Complicated,
My mom, Eunchae, all so complicated.
Minju! Your hubby is about to die
from all these complications.
Why are you yelling?
Why are you yelling at me?
What did I ever do to you?
You messed up today.
To Seo-kyeong and Muhyeok.
You did them wrong, big time.
That brat has changed. Definitely.
Is she dating Muhyeok?
Whatever! Go ahead! Date him!
Like cockroaches that are perfect for each other.
Then what was that about her liking me?
She has no principles.
If you let her comfort me for the time I have left...
If you'll let me have her for my remaining days...
I could go in peace.
I love you. It just happened that way.
[My Yun]
Recipient did not answer.
♪ When mom goes to the island shore to get food ♪
♪ The baby watches the house alone ♪
Galchi, shh!
Her temperature has decreased quite a bit now.
Did you finish solving the math problems I gave you?
Why is it so complicated?
I can't solve it.
Are you sure this is elementary school-level math?
Yes.
Empty your mind.
Stop thinking about that guy.
Concentrate only on the ball.
- Hey, listen!
- My name's not hey. It's Kang Hyeonwu.
Hyeonwu.
Don't move your wrist or your arm.
Move your shoulder!
Don't look at the ball flying when you hit it.
Keep looking at the ground!
Nice.
I'm sorry, Mister.
Get in.
Minju, open the door!
Open the door.
Who is the bastard next to you?
Who's that bastard sitting next to you?
Open the door!
Minju! Open it right now! Please!
Minju!
Open the door, please!
Open the door!
Oh my gosh! Oh my!
Uncle!
Get on my back.
[Text from Yun: Eunchae, I don't want to live anymore]
[Deleting message]
[Episode 9 Preview]
There's somewhere you and I have to go to together.
[Sorry, he is becoming closer to me]
[But my heart has changed now...]
[Love, Now I see her only]
[But to me, she is sadness]
Put me down!
I won't go! I said I'm not going!
That's a lot of tears for someone
who didn't drink any water.
Stop the car.
Would you rather eat or kiss me?
Stop the car, now!
Would you rather eat or sleep with me?
Would you rather eat? Or just live with me?
Would you rather eat?
Or would you rather...
die with me?
God.
If you do exist,
let me make a promise to you.
In the time I have left,
if I can have Eunchae next to me,
if Eunchae can comfort my remaining time,
I will quietly close my eyes.